(Howard:)-Sheldon?
-Zone.
(Leonard:)He'll figure it out
when he falls off the roof.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, I know you're in the zone,
but do you want some tea?
(Leonard:)All right, I can't believe
I'm gonna say this, but
(Leonard:)you haven't spoken in hours
and I'm starting to get worried.
(Leonard:)Please say something.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, prepare to be humbled
and weep at the glory of my genius.
(Leonard:)Nope, it was better before.
(Sheldon:)Look at it.
(Sheldon:)I feel like my mind just made a baby.
(Sheldon:)And it's beautiful.
(Sheldon:)It's not like human babies,
which are loud and covered in goop.
(Leonard:)Holy crap, Sheldon,
did you just figure out a method
(Leonard:)for synthesizing a new stable
super-heavy element?
(Sheldon:)Did I?
Well, that can't be right.
(Sheldon:)No one's ever done that before.
Except me, because I just did it!
♪ Sheldon and his brain, yeah!
Sheldon and his brain, yeah!